#### Curriculum vitae

### PERSONALINFORMATION

# Sandeep Raju Kolakaleti



Adelungstraße 39, 64283 Darmstadt, Germany

(+49) 15783206786 (+91) 7795533560

kolakaleti.sandeepraju@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sandeep-raju-kolakaleti-674469119/

Skype kolakaleti.sandeepraju@gmail.com

Website http://succomess.herokuapp.com/

Sex Male | Date of birth 4 Aug 1991 | Nationality Indian

JOB APPLIEDFOR Ser

Senior Front End Developer

**LANGUAGES** 

Telugu-C2 level, English-B2 level, Kannada- A2 level, Deutsch -A1 level

**SKILLS** 

HTML5, Css3, JavaScript, JQuery, ES6, AngularJs, Angular 10, Node.js, Typescript, Cordova, Bootstrap, Angular Material, Jasmine, Jest, Karma.js, protractor, Git, Svn, Tfs, Jira, Version one. Flexible in any operating systems (Windows, Mac, Linux) / Architectures.

JOB RELATED SKILLS

Excellent knowledge of quality control processes (currently responsible for quality) and Involved in SCRUM / AGILE methodologies, waterfall model, Solid Kiss principles. Proven mentoring skills as a specialist being responsible for the training for new technology team members.

INTRESTED/EXPOSURE ON

Challenging works like Node, js, Ionic, React, js, Vue, js, Php, Core Java, C#, Python and Sql or NoSql DB, AWS. Basically, I am a research developer and being update to date myself every time.

**CERTIFICATION** 

ANGULAR, REACT, MEAN Stack, AWS in Udemy online learning platform.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

15/05/2020 - present

Front-end Developer Freelancer (May 2020 - Aug 2021), Full Time Employee (Sep 2021)

SV Gebäudeautomation GmbH (Germany)

Projects: Quartiers, Driver Log Book, Warehouse Inventory Managment

Key skills and responsibilities: Angular 10, Angular material, HTML5, SCSS, Js, C# Entity, Capacitor Typescript, Docker, Ionic capacitor, Github. Worked and involved on angular 8 based apps and upgraded to 10.

Involved on coding from the scratch. Converted Angular material app to mobile support using Ionic Capacitor. Involved on client requirments/enhancements, Analysis, Implementation, Testing.

31/07/2018 - 15/05/2020

Technology Specialist

Wells Fargo Pvt Ltd, Bangalore (India)

Projects: Wealth Mobile Advisor and Wealth X.

Key skills and responsibilities: Angular 7/8, Angular material, HTML5, SCSS, CSS3,

JavaScript, Typescript, C# Entity Framework, MySQL, Cordova.

Worked and involved in migration tasks like upgrading the angular 4 to angular 7 to angular 8. Involved in code review process. My work efforts make the project and client more value added.

01/03/2016 - 25/05/2018

Senior Software Engineer

Mindtree Ltd, Bangalore (India)

Projects: ABG (Avis Budget Group) and Mercator

Key skills and responsibilities: AngularJs, Angular 4, Html5, SCSS, CSS3, JavaScript, Typescript.

Worked and involved to bring the Architecture design more readable and involved on factory design pattern

21/09/2015 - 28/02/2016

Software Engineer

Ionidea Interactive solutions Pvt Ltd, Bangalore (India)

Project: Eview Lite Framework

Key skills and responsibilities: JavaScript, HTML, CSS and AngularJs.

Worked and involved in maintaining the custom directive widget (button, table, collapsible drop down,) components which provided service to an own product Eview lite framework of Huawei client.

#### Curriculum vitae

#### 01/08/2014 - 19/09/2015

## Software Engineer

Unilog Software Solutions Pvt Ltd, Mysore (India)

Project: XRF100

Key skills and responsibilities: HTML5, CSS3, JQuery, JavaScript, Java Jersey Worked and involved in end-to-end Design Architecture, written the code from the scratch and

#### 11/11/2013 - 31/07/2014

## Associate consultant - Software Engineer (Client location: Unilog Software)

Vibrant Infosystems Pvt Ltd, Mysore (India)

Projects: Metadata repository for airport shop over, Gerrie App

Key skills and responsibilities: JQuery, JQuery mobile, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, PhoneGap.

Worked and involved using phone-gap supported JQuery mobile and Intel Appmobi frameworks and also I developed responsive complex design screens in web and mobile based hybrid Applications.

## **EDUCATION**

#### 01/05/2008 - 01/05/2012

## **Bachelor Degree**

EQF level6

Matrix Institute of Technology, JNTU Hyderabad University, Hyderabad (India)

General Computer Science Engineer (CSE) course with 72 % distinction score in Computer web technologies.

## 01/03/2006 - 01/03/2008

# Pre-university course

EQF level5

Surya Junior College, Jangareddygudem (India) General MPC course with 76% distinction score

Maths, Physics, Chemistry

### 01/03/2005 - 01/03/2006

# Secondary School Certificate

EOF level4

Surya High School, Jangareddygudem (India)

General course with 65%

English, Maths, Telugu, Science, Hindi, Social

## Organizational / managerial skills

Experienced team player with excellent communication and interpersonal skills who has the ability to not only work independently, but also can lead, motivate and positively influence team members as well as successfully mentor subordinates. I am always interested in volunteering for team member (building) activities and celebrations, as I believe leadership nurtures the overall success of any company.